A Guide to the Talmage DeWitte Foster Papers, 1925-1950
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Talmage DeWitte Foster Papers, 1925-1950
The Library of Virginia
50869
3.325 cubic feet (8 boxes).
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Teacher applications and some correspondence are restricted for 75 years from date of creation.
Acquisition Information
Purchased.
Biographical Information
Talmage DeWitte Foster was born in Bertrand, Lancaster County, Virginia on 28 March 1896. He was the son of Luther B. Foster (1860-1930) and India Carter (1856-1936). He served in World War I in the military police corps. Foster earned his bachelor and master degrees at the College of William and Mary. He then moved to Sussex County, where he served as superintendent of schools for 35 years. Foster married Margaret Waterfield (1902-1999). He died in Richmond on 23 January 1960, and is buried in Waverly Cemetery in Sussex County.
Scope and Content
Papers, 1925-1950, of Talmage DeWitte Foster (1896-1960), relating to his duties as superintendent of schools for Sussex County, Virginia. Includes correspondence, lists of teachers, publications, school enrollment reports, and teacher applications.
The majority of the collection consists of correspondence and applications submitted for teacher and school principal positions. There is incoming and outgoing correspondence with applicants, letters from Foster to college deans seeking qualified candidates, and to college placement bureaus seeking credentials on individuals. The application forms include personal data, educational history, courses taken, experience, and references. There are letters of recommendation, resumes, college transcripts, and photographs. The correspondence and applications are divided by "white" and "colored" applicants. There is a name index to the applications included in the finding aid to the collection.
The collection also includes letters to and from Thomas D. Eason (1887-1939) of the Virginia Department of Education regarding mainly teacher examinations and certification, and there is also a good deal of correspondence with Eley Marshall Estes (1897-1960), who was principal of the Wakefield Agricultural High School, and also includes annual reports, teaching plans, schedules, and supervised practice work reports of the school.
Contents List
- College Entrance Examination. (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Correspondence - "Colored," 1944. (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Correspondence - "Colored," 1945. (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Correspondence - "Colored," 1946. (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Correspondence - "Colored," 1947. (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Correspondence - "Colored," 1948. (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Correspondence - "Colored," 1949. (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Correspondence - "White" (S), 1926-1942. (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Correspondence - "White" (T), 1926-1942. (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Correspondence - "White" (U-V), 1926-1942. (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Correspondence - "White," 1944. (Box 1, Folder 11-13)
- Correspondence - "White," 1945. (Box 1, Folder 14-15)
- Correspondence - "White," 1946. (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Correspondence - "White," 1947. (Box 2, Folder 2-3)
- Correspondence - "White," 1948. (Box 2, Folder 4-5)
- Correspondence - "White," 1949. (Box 2, Folder 6-7)
- Coulbourn, U. Oscar. (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Eason, Thomas D., 1925-1939. (Box 2, Folder 9-11)
- Estes, Eley Marshall, 1925-1934. (Box 3, Folder 1-2)
- Extension Courses, 1931-1932. (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Laidlaw Brothers Publishers. (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Lists of Teachers - "Colored," 1943-1945. (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Lists of Teachers - "White," 1943-1948. (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Miscellaneous. (Box 3, Folder 7)
- National Youth Administration - Student Work Program, 1940. (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Publications. (Box 8)
- Publishers Invoices, 1938. (Box 3, Folder 9)
- School Enrollment Reports - "Colored," 1944-1947. (Box 3, Folder 10-13)
- Teacher Applications - "Colored," 1943.
- Nowlin, Irma Louise. (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Teacher Applications - "Colored," 1944.
- Akers, Mae H.. (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Banner, Roland R.. (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Bell, Mamie M.. (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Brown, Ethel Irene. (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Clarke, W. S.. (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Coley, Mary Heloise. (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Flournoy, B. C. (Mrs.). (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Garner, Richard Lee (Mrs.). (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Graves, Juanita. (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Green, Roxie Vialance. (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Harris, Mary Lou. (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Harrison, Frances Vera. (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Hill, Mable. (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Honablue, Ella Louise. (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Hoskie, Rosa Lee Copeland. (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Jeffries, Theresa Johnson. (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Jerkins, Alease Jones. (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Jones, Matilda Shields. (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Magbie, Wilbur D.. (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Maske, Edna Earl. (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Moye, Willie Mae. (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Rainey, Mary V.. (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Robertson, Willie Mae. (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Robinson, Dulcenia W.. (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Salmon, Hazel Lee. (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Simmons, Eva G.. (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Stephens, Louise. (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Stewart, A. E. (Miss). (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Tate, Elyse James. (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Taylor, Florine. (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Thomas, Eleanor. (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Townes, Fannie E. (Mrs.). (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Tate, Elyse James. (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Wiggins, Lake E.. (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Williams, M. F. (Mrs.). (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Teacher Applications - "Colored," 1945.
- Clarke, Jannie Andrews H.. (Box 4, Folder 1)
- DeVane, Herbert M.. (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Holloman, Mary M.. (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Lomax, N. Elleen. (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Powell, Maude C. (Mrs.). (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Sloan, Geneva Ettalie. (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Teacher Applications - "Colored," 1946.
- Backus, Audrye V.. (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Boykin, Perry W.. (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Broady, Frances Blanche. (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Brooks, John L.. (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Brooks, Rosetta H.. (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Brown, Arlethia E.. (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Brown, Juanita. (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Cheeks, Mermon E.. (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Coles, Nancy Lee. (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Cooke, Delma L.. (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Crawford, Vera Belle. (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Cunningham, Grace. (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Curtis, Georgia R.. (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Dabney, Daisey J. (Mrs.). (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Fitzgerald, Loisteine Rebecca. (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Fulford, Florine T. (Mrs.). (Box 4, Folder 3)
- George, Cora L.. (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Goode, Harry Carter. (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Hairston, Almeta Ann. (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Hall, Ethel H. (Mrs.). (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Jiggetts, Louise Friend. (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Johnson, Christina M.. (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Johnson, Kate H.. (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Jones, William N.. (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Knox, Ernestine R. (Mrs.). (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Lawrence, Bertha L.. (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Mabrey, Lenard B.. (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Macklin, Laura Elizabeth. (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Madison, Alfreda L.. (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Mays, Agnes. (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Miles, Blanche O.. (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Miller, Edmonia R. (Mrs.). (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Myrick, Anna Beale. (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Porter, Virtley Allmond. (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Reid, Maggie. (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Saunders, Annie. (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Smith, Margretta E.. (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Stephens, Louise. (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Swann, Hazel. (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Sweets, Georgia Patrick. (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Venable, Vanessa R.. (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Williams, Mamie A.. (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Teacher Applications - "Colored," 1947.
- Akers, Mae Hunter. (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Allgood, Earl Vann. (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Anthony, Edna L.. (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Banks, Thelma F.. (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Bond, Mamie E.. (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Botts, Empsie Taylor (Mrs.). (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Bowen, Helen L.. (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Bowman, James A.. (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Boykin, Dorothy Louise. (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Briggs, Vina E.. (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Broadnax, Geraldine B.. (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Brown, Doris Lee. (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Brown, Eula C. (Mrs.). (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Capehart, Sarah J.. (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Claud, Eunice O. (Mrs.). (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Cottrell, Pocahontas E.. (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Curley, Audrey M.. (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Curley, E. Otelia. (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Davis, Veronica M.. (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Edler, Izetta D.. (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Edwards, Sidney H.. (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Exum, Mary B.. (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Fisher, Eunice Mae. (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Henry, Clara L.. (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Howard, Vernice E.. (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Jackson, Mary Virginia. (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Jerkins, Kenneth. (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Johnaon, Grace Claiborne (Mrs.). (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Jones, Ernest W.. (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Jordan, Virginia. (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Lee, Florence H.. (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Lewis, Earl W.. (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Lightfoot, Rhoda L.. (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Lloyd, Dorcas B.. (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Lomax, Marie R.. (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Martin, Dorothy Moore. (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Mayfield, Edyth Jones. (Box 4, Folder 8)
- McDaniels, Juanita. (Box 4, Folder 8)
- McQueen, Helen Elnora. (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Myrick, Bernice. (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Norfleet, Thelma T.. (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Oliver, Mary J.. (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Oliver, Ulysses L.. (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Overton, Clarence A.. (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Patterson, Annie T. (Mrs.). (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Pope, Elsie Mae. (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Porter, Lillian B. (Mrs.). (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Pope, Elsie Mae. (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Powell, Hattie S.. (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Pruden, Johnola S.. (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Ridley, Virginia Mason. (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Rivers, Anna Ray. (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Russell, Mattie. (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Scott, Mildred Juanita. (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Simmons, Walter Lee (Miss). (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Toyer, Mary Elaine. (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Vann, Solomon M.. (Box 4, Folder 9)
- White, Clara L.. (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Yokley, Ralph L.. (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Young, Bernice W.. (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Young, James Thomas. (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Teacher Applications - "Colored," 1948.
- Bailey, John F., Jr.. (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Baysmore, Viola. (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Bennett, Eleanor Smith. (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Blount, Elsie Virginia. (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Booth, Beatrice O.. (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Boothe, Irene Olivia. (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Braye, Alice Eula. (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Brown, Eula C.. (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Brown, Gladys B. (Mrs.). (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Browne, Flossie W.. (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Browne, Johnnie A. V. (Miss). (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Christian, E. R. (Miss). (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Clarke, Bettye R.. (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Coleman, Geneva L.. (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Coleman, Georgia Sophronia. (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Coles, Mary Gwendolyn. (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Cowling, Dorothy M.. (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Cox, Martha Ann. (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Daugherty, Elizabeth C.. (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Douglas, Ruth (Mrs.). (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Doyle, Elsie Richardson. (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Edmonds, Ruth M.. (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Flanagan, Cassie Lee. (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Godfrey, Catherine I.. (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Green, Clinton Wallace. (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Gregory, Evelyn Ann. (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Halloway, Bernire Virginia. (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Hardy, Athylone Warren. (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Hatchett, George O.. (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Jackson, Adolphus O.. (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Jackson, Caledonia. (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Jenkins, Lillie Mae. (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Joyner, Georgia Rose. (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Ledbetter, Latina C.. (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Lomax, Albert A.. (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Lomax, Katie Louise. (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Millner, Hensile. (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Peace, Ruth O.. (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Pegram, Doris Mae. (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Poole, Doris Elizabeth. (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Reavis, William. (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Robinson, Catherine O'Neal. (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Robinson, Margaret A. D.. (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Robinson, Willis B.. (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Rodriguez, Ruth B.. (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Sampson, Shirley. (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Simpkins, Leona Kilgo. (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Smith, Dorothy M.. (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Southerland, Sylvia V.. (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Stephens, Carrie J.. (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Stith, Louise S.. (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Taylor, Ernestine J.. (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Thomas, Jennie L.. (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Thompson, Louis W., Jr.. (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Tignor, Alida B.. (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Vaughan, Ethel C.. (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Walker, Howard Stewart. (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Wheeler, Gloria Elizabeth. (Box 5, Folder 4)
- White, Clara L.. (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Williams, Charlotte Wilhelmina. (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Williams, Russell R.. (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Winder, Marian Audrey. (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Wood, Edward G.. (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Wyche, Mary. (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Young, Maisy E.. (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Younge, Varnceil. (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Teacher Applications - "Colored," 1949.
- Freeman, Edith V.. (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Hawkins, John, Jr.. (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Ray, Rachel I.. (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Waters, Harry C.. (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Teacher Applications - "Colored," 1950.
- Lockett, Hettie B.. (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Teacher Applications - "White" (C), 1926-1942.
- Cox, Virginia Lee (1928). (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Teacher Applications - "White" (S), 1926-1942.
- Sater, Elsye Tash (1938). (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Savedge, Evalyn (1936). (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Scales, Mary Elizabeth (1936). (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Scarborough, Ruth (1928?). (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Scordo, Samuel J. (1939). (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Scott, Armistead Jane (1932). (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Scott, Mildred M. (1937). (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Seaborne, Edith (1932). (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Sears, Mary Grey (1935). (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Seward, William W., Jr. (1936). (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Sharpe, Thelma G. (1928). (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Shelton, Nollie W. (1934). (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Shorter, Fannie B. (1937). (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Shortt, E. C. (1938). (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Shelburne, Robert C. (1936). (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Simmons, Alma (1935). (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Simmons, Bettie L. (1935). (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Skillman, Ellen (1937). (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Slater, Mary Elizabeth (1937). (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Slocomb, Sara Wessells (1936). (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Smith, Frances Crafton (1935). (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Smith, Margaret Hill (1937). (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Snodgrass, Clyde E. (1935). (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Snodgrass, Katherine E. (1937). (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Spain, Virginia Willis (1937). (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Sparks, Nancy C. (1935). (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Spencer, Georgia (1934?). (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Spiers, Kathryn (1936). (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Spratley, Mabel E. (1929). (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Stainman, Ben (1935). (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Stephenson, Ava M. (1928). (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Stephenson, Frances Elizabeth (1935). (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Stephenson, Verice (1934). (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Stevens, Mary Fairfax (1937). (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Stevenson, Elizabeth L. (1936). (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Stone, Mildred Marie (1938). (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Story, Cornelia (1938). (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Stovall, J. P. (1935?). (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Straughn, Fannie Weymouth (1938). (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Stubs, Elizabeth (1936). (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Swineford, Sancta Mae (1934). (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Teacher Applications - "White" (T), 1926-1942.
- Tankard, Florence M. (1936). (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Taylor, Frances C. (1941). (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Taylor, Henrietta (1933). (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Taylor, Irene (1936). (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Terrell, A. L. (1932). (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Terretta, Mary (1935). (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Terretta, Polly (1932). (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Terrie, Nelda Ann (1938). (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Thomas, C. P. (1939). (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Thomas, Helen (1930). (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Thomas, Martha E. (1939). (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Thomas, Norris L. (1932). (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Thompson, Agnes (1937). (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Thompson, Elizabeth Mosby (1936). (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Thompson, Frank L. (1939). (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Thompson, John P. (1939). (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Thompson, Margaret E. (1937). (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Thompson, Nan (1940). (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Tillery, Frances Ann (1935). (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Tindell, Edith Cory (1939). (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Tisdale, Lucy (1937). (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Tisdale, Margaret (1937). (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Tobias, Louis (1938). (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Tomko, Lena (1936). (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Tomko, Ruth M. (1936). (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Transon, Lucile V. (1942). (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Trimmer, Osie (1942). (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Truitt, Elizabeth (1941). (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Tuck, Virginia Sue (1939). (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Tucker, Margaret Randolph (1939). (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Tudor, Evelyn W. (1936). (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Turner, Annie H. (1939). (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Turner, Bettie McClung (1941). (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Turnes, Virginia C. (1938). (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Tyns, Jona (1927). (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Teacher Applications - "White" (U-V), 1926-1942.
- Underwood, J. T. (1934). (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Teacher Applications - "White," 1944.
- Albright, Betty. (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Clardy, Jenny May. (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Clark, Anne Lenoir. (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Cox, William J.. (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Curtis, Helen M.. (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Elam, Rosemary Virginia. (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Gatling, Margaret Chappell (Mrs.). (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Griffin, L. H. and E. M.. (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Hatcher, William B.. (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Lewis, Lucille. (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Neaves, Carrie M. (Mrs.). (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Piland, Woodrow Wilson. (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Pool, Ella. (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Ramey, Ruth. (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Ricks, D. C. (Mrs.). (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Scott, Annie Holt. (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Seward, Mary Virginia. (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Sharp, Eva (Mrs.). (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Smith, Frances Lee. (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Steele, Blanche. (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Thornton, Dunreath. (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Tiller, Juanita. (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Tindell, Edith C.. (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Watts, Virginia. (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Wheeler, Jessie (Mrs.). (Box 6, Folder 4)
- White, Louise Batte (Mrs.). (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Wilkinson, Edna M.. (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Teacher Applications - "White," 1945.
- Apperson, Cornelius J.. (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Blackwell, Betty C.. (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Bryant, S. Roy. (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Copley, Mary Roberts. (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Darby, Nancy C.. (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Edwards, Elizabeth. (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Francis, Samuel N.. (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Gibbs, C. Glynwood. (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Hamlin, Anne. (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Huckstep, C. T.. (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Jarratt, Elizabeth A.. (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Lashley, Ethel Gilliam. (Box 6, Folder 6)
- LeCompte, Isabel Mason. (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Lee, Louise. (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Lyles, Arthur D.. (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Parson, Virginia. (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Ramsey, Curtis L.. (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Salmon, Sue Pearce (Mrs.). (Box 6, Folder 6)
- See, Robert G., Jr.. (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Thompson, Elsie. (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Tignor, John M.. (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Tyler, Estelle Ironmonger. (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Teacher Applications - "White," 1946.
- Boothe, Carolyn. (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Brown, Arthur H., Jr.. (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Burdick, Thelma Elizabeth. (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Darden, Rufus H.. (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Dove, Mary Anne. (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Dumville, Samuel Hall. (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Ellis, Elsie Dunn (Mrs.). (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Elwang, Nell Holloway. (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Foster, Lloyd L.. (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Gillis, Thomas Herbert. (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Hillman, Franklin P.. (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Hillman, L. W.. (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Johnson, Jacob Lee. (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Lawson, Betty Barksdale. (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Leavitt, Jerome. (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Morgan, Samuel Clarke. (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Richardson, John W. (Mrs.) Gladys Sheppard. (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Timmer, Osie. (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Webb, Marjorie. (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Teacher Applications - "White," 1947.
- Atkinson, Harold L.. (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Beale, Elsie A.. (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Benedett, Bill. (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Benedett, Peggy Ratliff. (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Brown, Margaret A.. (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Caldwell, Joe Scott. (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Cavalier, Anthony M., Jr.. (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Cobb, Alice P. (Mrs.). (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Cosby, Hortense. (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Dickerson, Mary Lee. (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Easley, William K.. (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Hall, Jean Suter. (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Joyner, India Butler. (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Joyner, Rachel. (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Kilgore, William. (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Lyons, Claudia. (Box 7, Folder 3)
- McCauley, Nancy C.. (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Smith, Nellie Shackleford. (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Stanley, Annie M.. (Box 7, Folder 3)
- West, Charlotte. (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Wilds, Alice Mae. (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Teacher Applications - "White," 1948.
- Bondurant, Mary Elizabeth. (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Burroughs, Robert C.. (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Davis, Betty I.. (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Matthews, Margaret. (Box 7, Folder 4)
- McDaniel, Margaret. (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Perkins, Leonard (Mrs.). (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Powell, Martha C.. (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Presson, Amanda Wilson. (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Robertson, Elizabeth. (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Sharp, Hessie A.. (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Skinner, Charles. (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Teacher Applications - "White," 1949.
- Abernathy, H. S.. (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Addison, Jesse William, Jr.. (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Comerford, Laura Jean. (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Cornett, Joanna. (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Dufford, Russell T., Jr.. (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Harman, Iris. (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Hawkins, Myrtle M. (Mrs.). (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Heartwell, Elizabeth Hillsman. (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Lewis, Beverly Hope. (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Mahone, Mary A. (Mrs.). (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Mangum, Edwin W.. (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Mattox, Joyce. (Box 7, Folder 6)
- McGlothlin, Francis. (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Puryear, William H.. (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Ross, Dolores May. (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Seymour, Jacqueline. (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Spencer, June. (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Wilkinson, Rachel. (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Temple Motor Sales. (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Virginia Association of School Trustees, 1 May 1944. (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Wakefield Agricultural High School - Annual Reports. (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Wakefield Agricultural High School - Project/Teaching Plans. (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Wakefield Agricultural High School - Schedules/Calendars of Work. (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Wakefield Agricultural High School - Status of Improved Farming Practices. (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Wakefield Agricultural High School - Supervised Practice Work Reports. (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Wakefield Agricultural High School - Travel Statements. (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Wakefield Agricultural High School - Visitation Reports. (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Waverly School Plant Addition, 1032. (Box 7, Folder 16)